https://www.exportersindia.com/privacy-policy.htm

JavaScript is disabled in your browser. Enable JavaScript for full functionality of this site.
To know how to enable JavaScript in your web browser click here.
Privacy   Policy
Home
/
Privacy & Policy
The website, www.exportersindia.com (ExportersIndia.Com) is an electronic web based platform for exchanging, exploring and enhancing business online by searching and interacting with suitable companies. It is owned and managed by Weblink .IN Pvt. Ltd. ("Company") with its registered office at 33 & 33A, Rama Road, Industrial Area, Near Kirti Nagar Metro Station, New Delhi, 110015 (India).
ExportersIndia.Com is committed to safeguarding the privacy of its Users. All our users are requested to read the following Privacy Policy to have a complete understanding regarding how their personal & business information will be treated, as they associate themselves with ExportersIndia.Com and make full use of our services to further their business interests. This policy is exclusively applicable on the entire platform operated by ExportersIndia.Com and not beyond.
ExportersIndia.Com may amend these policies at any time by posting the amended version on this site. Such amended version shall automatically be effective upon its posting on this site. You are advised to check this section of regular intervals to be updated on developments.
Information Collection - Business & Personal:
ExportersIndia.Com collects information from its Users at the time of registration as well as at certain specific instances of usage of our services wherein they are requested to provide with their personal and business information including contact information. These forms usually seek information such as name, email address, contact modes and specifics along with the business information including company details, services and requirements.
As an User using the free / paid services of ExportersIndia.Com, it is deemed that the User has granted ExportersIndia.Com the right to use the posted information , publish the desired details throughout its platform i.e. all divisions / sister concerns / ventures of Exportersindia.com including and not limited to directories, leads sections, catalogs, listing, website pages etc.
The personal information requested by ExportersIndia.Com, is for usage at ExportersIndia.com alone, unless it is specifically stated otherwise or if you choose to share it with some User / Visitor / Third Party explicitly.
Promotions through Banner Advertisements & Emails that are run on ExportersIndia.Com may be sponsored by companies other than ExportersIndia.Com or may be co-sponsored by ExportersIndia.Com and another company. During a promotion, some or all of the data may be shared with the sponsor. However, you can decide not to participate in the promotion if you don't want your data to be shared and mail us as feedback@exportersindia.com
In order to improve the user experience and provide better services, we gather and analyse the usage statistics such as number of unique visitors, pages viewed, screen resolution, browser software etc.
Personal & Business Information Usage:
ExportersIndia.Com collects personal or public information with the intent to improve the user experience on its website with the aim that the Users are benefitted by the better services such as personalized support, interactive interfaces and communication etc. which are generally free services though some add-ons could be paid. The business information shared by the User is used to display the User’s products and services via the business listings, catalogs, website etc. with the sole purpose of creating an online business presence.
Based on the User’s site usage statistics, trends and requirements, ExportersIndia.Com serves the Users with requisite free services, advertisements and user experience through its website, customised mailers and general newsletters. The User’s personal and business information is displayed at ExportersIndia.com which allows the other buyers / sellers to reach out with their business enquiries through email, phone calls, SMS or Whatsapp which may or may not be particularly matched to the User’s interest and requirements since ExportersIndia.Com doesn’t exercise any control over its Users for sending business enquiries to the listed members.
We record browsing, search, requirement posting and buying activities of our Users including but not limited to their client's contact details and profiles to use the same to provide value-added services to our Users.
To extend value-added services to our Users, we record the buying and browsing activities of our Users including and not limited to their search patterns, client contact details and profiles.
Virtual Numbers may / shall be assigned to Free & Paid Members and incorporated in the displays at all divisions/sister concerns/ventures of ExportersIndia.Com, and it can be used for listing and display at other places and portals including Third Party Service Providers and Search Engines. ExportersIndia.Com will record and track the calls via these numbers and use the same to provide value-added services to the Users.
Information Distribution
ExportersIndia.com makes a constant endeavour to improve the online platform and make it more efficient, relevant, innovative and in sync with the current trends and technologies. ExportersIndia.com may from time to time send mails or make feedback calls to its Users regarding its products and services which may be obtained from the automated match-making tools based on User preference, activity etc. ExportersIndia.com may shoot direct mails using its own scripts (without disclosing the email address) with respect/pertaining to the products and services of third parties that it feels may be of interest to the User or if the user has shown interest in your company for business requirement by way of our paid buyers-sellers contact services.
Only ExportersIndia.com, its registered members or its employees working under confidentiality agreements will send these direct mailers. Relevancy of the contacts made between Users would depend upon the information sought & given by various Users.
Information Sharing
ExportersIndia.com doesn’t disclose or share any of the User’s personally identifiable information unless under special circumstances or if already permitted by the User or if requested by a government or law enforcement body or as permitted in terms of this Privacy Policy.
To avoid extraction by email extractors, ExportersIndia.com does not display the User’s email addresses though the same may be shared by the Users themselves or be available on the User’s own website linked via the business listing / catalogs at ExportersIndia.com.
ExportersIndia.Com may also disclose the User's identity and contact information in special cases to cooperate fully with governmental authorities, law enforcement body, private investigators and/or injured third parties in the investigation of any suspected criminal or civil wrongdoing.
Furthermore, ExportersIndia.Com may disclose information as a result of a subpoena or other legal action or bring legal action against someone who may be violating the rights or property of ExportersIndia.com or its Users or if deemed necessary for the maintenance, upgradation, servicing or improvement of the services extended at ExportersIndia.com.
The personal information collected may be transferred and shared in case of sale as well.
Updation of Information
A user may edit his/her account information and profile by logging into his My Folder at ExportersIndia.Com and the changes would be displayed with the completion of necessary verifications.
A user account can be deleted or deactivated, but doing so will result in the User not being able to access any of the services. Residual information will remain within our archive records.
Information Protection
At no point does ExportersIndia.com be involved in any sale of data in bulk or otherwise to any third party wherein it can be misused for telemarketing / telesales / email marketing etc. In addition, ExportersIndia.com does not sell any User's personal information or business information until and unless it is permitted by the User.
The statistics provided to prospective advertisers or partners or sponsors is only the aggregated User preferences / trends and does not include any personally identifiable information about any individual User.
It is advised that the Users safeguard their details, sign out from their folders and share information only after they have sure of the receivers intent. This is to ensure that others cannot access their personal or business information and correspondence. It is important especially if the user shares the computer with someone else or is using a computer in a public place.
ExportersIndia.com takes necessary steps, within its limits of commercial viability and necessity, to ensure that the User's information is treated securely. However, since no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure so though ExportersIndia.com strives to protect the User's personal & business information, it cannot ensure the security of any information transmitted to ExportersIndia.com and you do so at your own risk.
Once received, ExportersIndia.com makes best efforts to ensure its security in its systems. Please keep in mind that whenever you post personal & business information online, that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties.
Data Collection and Usage by Google
ExportersIndia.com runs Google ads on its platform. Using cookies it tracks and uses the visits of the Users on our site as well as other sites on the basis of which it serves content and ads.
Terms of Usage for Mobile App Users
The ExportersIndia App can be downloaded from Google Play or App Store. Constant upgrades and modifications on App shall be a norm as ExportersIndia.com puts in all efforts on improving the user experience and efficiency of the App. The User agrees to download the updates as and when they arrive to make the best use of the App.
The App’s ability to function to its full potential is dependent on the User’s device as well as connection used. ExportersIndia.com cannot be held liable for such issues along with the data charges, roaming charges etc. as applicable which are related to the mobile network provider.
Each User agrees that it shall not copy, reproduce, modify or create versions of the App, text and images for the purpose of re-selling or re-distributing, operating a business that competes with ExportersIndia.Com, or otherwise commercially exploiting the ExportersIndia.Com Content. The App, the trademarks, copyrights and all other intellectual properties solely belong to ExportersIndia.com. The app is for purely for personal usage and the User is solely responsible for maintaining confidentiality and keeping their phone and App secure.
App – Data Collection, Usage, Protection and Updation
The Users shall be requested to provide with their personal and business information including contact information. Information such as name, email address, phone numbers, mobile specifications, contact modes and specifics along with the business information including company details, services and requirements may be assimilated.
The App shall access the User’s location to provide demographically suitable results. The App may access the phone contacts to save a lead’s contact in the User’s device. The User data may be used on individual basis to provide better user experience or on aggregated basis to improve the App. ExportersIndia.com may also share offers and communications based on your viewing, buying, selling preferences as well as App usage trends. The User needs to keep all the relevant information updated while using the App so as to make the best use of the services.
The services on the App may vary slightly from the website owing to the variation in devices. There are certain free and paid features which may not be incorporated in the mobile application version though they are a part of the original website since the mobile apps are designed to be compact and light to ensure a smooth experience. Each User hereby represents, warrants and agrees that the same shall be acceptable as a matter of fact and no requests to incorporate any such feature in the mobile app version would be initiated by the Users.
The App is currently a free version though it may be on paid basis in the future and this shift would be done with pre-intimation. ExportersIndia.com may also chose to temporarily or permanently terminate the App services at any time without prior notice.
Browse By Categories
Agriculture
Apparel & Fashion
Automotive & Auto Parts
Ayurvedic & Herbal Products
Business Services
Chemicals
Computers & PC Hardware
